Hatim Laajini

Project Manager, Designer, Marketing Specialist and Full Stack Developer Well-qualified Project Manager familiar with wide range of implementation, operations and Marketing Strategies and languages.

Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements, in addition to CMS, EDM platforms, graphic design and multiple Marketing tools.

Contact

Address

Istanbul, Kadikoy, 34110

Phone

541-249-2756

E-mail

hatim.jini@gmail.com

Portfolio

https://dev-hl.online/

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hatim-laajini-b46b4a21

Skills

Proficiency

Ruby On rails

CSS
proficiency

JavaScript
programming

ReactJs
Proficiency

MSQL,
POSTGRESQL



Work History

2022-06

Current

Project Manager – Whitenoisethelabel.com

- Built the operation system of the company, shipping contracts, Production pipeline, packaging and pricing.
- Managed the content team of seven members to ensure the delivery of the work and feasibility of the campaigns.
- Put in place POS system for two distribution points in Dubai and trained the sales team to use it.
- Developed multiples websites for the brand using ReactJS, NextJS.
- Designed the brand's visuals and social media feed, promotion content and investors presentations.

2020-06 -Current

Full Stack Developer

Goadway.com, Istanbul

- Enquired and managed a portfolio of customers.
- Boosted network, by reaching out to more customers and maintain fruitful relation for both sides
- Designed UX/UI on Figma/Illustrator to match the brand identity of the company.
- Managed a team of three, graphic designers and Digital Marketing Specialists.
- Developed user-oriented visuals and features using frontend languages to increase site traffic.
- Developed landing pages, dashboards and online applications using React, Ruby on Rails. Worked on more than
- 10 projects on different fields

Tailwind,
Bootstrap &
Ant design

Languages

English
Excellent

French
Excellent

Arabic
Excellent

Turkish
Very Good

Spanish
Average

2016-07 -2021-07

Language Consultant

New York Studio Istanbul, Istanbul, Kadikoy

- Proofread, edited and improved documents of different sizes.
- Interpreted/translated conversations simultaneously to help both parties conduct business, handle medical needs or manage personal concerns.
- Worked with students of different ages, children, teenagers, and Adults.
- Provided business oriented lessons for Siemens, Cinema
 Mars, HSBC ... personal, in Marketing, HR and production.

2018-06 -2021-04

Project Manager

Beyaz Dis Ticaret, Istanbul, Kadikoy

- Secured relation with key wholesale customers and buyers.
- Worked on the vision of the company and delivered a forecast of the company's potential
- Pitched and assisted the creation of company branch in NYS, USA.
- Developed and initiated projects, managed costs, and monitored performance of the team.
- Identified, reviewed and applied policies and procedures, In addition to implementation of tools such us, Monday.com, Trello and Milanote.
- Modified and directed project plans to meet organizational needs.
- Maintained open communication by presenting regular updates on project status to customers. Achieved sales target
- of 1.2 M \$ for years 2019 and 2020

Education

Online Full Stack Developer Bachelor:
Full Stack Developer

Full Stack Developer

Open Class Rooms - France

2009-09 - BTS in Marketing – Agadir Morocco
2011-07 Institute Specialized Technology Applied Hotel & Tourism



Graphic Design

Drawing

Music Recording

Underground Rock Musician